[
  {
    "id": "rama",
    "complexity": 1,
    "question": "ರಾಮ",
    "answer": "राम",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Rāma"
  },
  {
    "id": "nala",
    "complexity": 1,
    "question": "ನಲ",
    "answer": "नल",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Nala"
  },
  {
    "id": "nila",
    "complexity": 1,
    "question": "ನೀಲ",
    "answer": "नील",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Nīla"
  },
  {
    "id": "lava",
    "complexity": 1,
    "question": "ಲವ",
    "answer": "लव",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Lava"
  },
  {
    "id": "kusha",
    "complexity": 1,
    "question": "ಕುಶ",
    "answer": "कुश",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Kusha"
  },
  {
    "id": "tara",
    "complexity": 1,
    "question": "ತಾರಾ",
    "answer": "तारा",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Tara"
  },
  {
    "id": "din",
    "complexity": 1,
    "question": "ದಿನ",
    "answer": "दिन",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Din"
  },
  {
    "id": "kal",
    "complexity": 1,
    "question": "ಕಲ",
    "answer": "कल",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Kal"
  },
  {
    "id": "aaj",
    "complexity": 1,
    "question": "ಆಜ",
    "answer": "आज",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Āj"
  },
  {
    "id": "am",
    "complexity": 1,
    "question": "ಆಮ",
    "answer": "आम",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Ām"
  },
  {
    "id": "sebab",
    "complexity": 1,
    "question": "ಸೇಬ",
    "answer": "सेब",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Seb"
  },
  {
    "id": "lal",
    "complexity": 1,
    "question": "ಲಾಲ",
    "answer": "लाल",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Lāl"
  },
  {
    "id": "seeta",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಸೀತಾ",
    "answer": "सीता",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Sītā"
  },
  {
    "id": "bharata",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಭರತ",
    "answer": "भरत",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Bharata"
  },
  {
    "id": "janaka",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಜನಕ",
    "answer": "जनक",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Janaka"
  },
  {
    "id": "hanuman",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಹನುಮಾನ",
    "answer": "हनुमान",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Hanumān"
  },
  {
    "id": "sugreeva",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಸುಗ್ರೀವ",
    "answer": "सुग्रीव",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Sugrīva"
  },
  {
    "id": "vali",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ವಾಲೀ",
    "answer": "वाली",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Vālī"
  },
  {
    "id": "angada",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಅಂಗದ",
    "answer": "अंगद",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Aṅgada"
  },
  {
    "id": "ravana",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ರಾವಣ",
    "answer": "रावण",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Rāvaṇa"
  },
  {
    "id": "narada",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ನಾರದ",
    "answer": "नारद",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Narada"
  },
  {
    "id": "garuda",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಗರುಡ",
    "answer": "गरुड़",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Garuda"
  },
  {
    "id": "pani",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಪಾನೀ",
    "answer": "पानी",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Pānī"
  },
  {
    "id": "khana",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಖಾನಾ",
    "answer": "खाना",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Khānā"
  },
  {
    "id": "skool",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಸ್ಕೂಲ",
    "answer": "स्कूल",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Skūl"
  },
  {
    "id": "kitaab",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಕಿತಾಬ",
    "answer": "किताब",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Kitāb"
  },
  {
    "id": "dost",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ದೋಸ್ತ",
    "answer": "दोस्त",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Dost"
  },
  {
    "id": "ghar",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಘರ",
    "answer": "घर",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Ghar"
  },
  {
    "id": "chai",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಚಾಯ",
    "answer": "चाय",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Chāy"
  },
  {
    "id": "aankh",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಆಁಖ",
    "answer": "आँख",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Ā̃kh"
  },
  {
    "id": "haath",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಹಾಥ",
    "answer": "हाथ",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Hāth"
  },
  {
    "id": "pair",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಪೈರ",
    "answer": "पैर",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Pair"
  },
  {
    "id": "kela",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಕೇಲಾ",
    "answer": "केला",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Kelā"
  },
  {
    "id": "angoor",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಅಂಗೂರ",
    "answer": "अंगूर",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Angoor"
  },
  {
    "id": "anar",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಅನಾರ",
    "answer": "अनार",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Anār"
  },
  {
    "id": "khara",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಖರ",
    "answer": "खर",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Khara"
  },
  {
    "id": "dilli",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ದಿಲ್ಲೀ",
    "answer": "दिल्ली",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Dillī"
  },
  {
    "id": "mumbai",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಮುಂಬಈ",
    "answer": "मुंबई",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Mumbaī"
  },
  {
    "id": "kerala",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಕೇರಲ",
    "answer": "केरल",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Kerala"
  },
  {
    "id": "karnataka",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಕರ್ನಾಟಕ",
    "answer": "कर्नाटक",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Karṇāṭaka"
  },
  {
    "id": "gujarat",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಗುಜರಾತ",
    "answer": "गुजरात",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Gujarāt"
  },
  {
    "id": "punjab",
    "complexity": 2,
    "question": "ಪಂಜಾಬ",
    "answer": "पंजाब",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Panjāb"
  },
  {
    "id": "lakshmana",
    "complexity": 3,
    "question": "ಲಕ್ಷ್ಮಣ",
    "answer": "लक्ष्मण",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Lakṣmaṇa"
  },
  {
    "id": "shatrughna",
    "complexity": 3,
    "question": "ಶತ್ರುಘ್ನ",
    "answer": "शत्रुघ्न",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Śatrughna"
  },
  {
    "id": "dasharatha",
    "complexity": 3,
    "question": "ದಶರಥ",
    "answer": "दशरथ",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Daśaratha"
  },
  {
    "id": "kausalyaa",
    "complexity": 3,
    "question": "ಕೌಸಲ್ಯಾ",
    "answer": "कौसल्या",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Kausalyā"
  },
  {
    "id": "kaikeyii",
    "complexity": 3,
    "question": "ಕೈಕೇಯೀ",
    "answer": "कैकेयी",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Kaikeyī"
  },
  {
    "id": "sumitra",
    "complexity": 3,
    "question": "ಸುಮಿತ್ರ",
    "answer": "सुमित्रा",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Sumitrā"
  },
  {
    "id": "vishvamitra",
    "complexity": 3,
    "question": "ವಿಶ್ವಾಮಿತ್ರ",
    "answer": "विश्वामित्र",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Viśvāmitra"
  },
  {
    "id": "agastya",
    "complexity": 3,
    "question": "ಅಗಸ್ತ್ಯ",
    "answer": "अगस्त्य",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Agastya"
  },
  {
    "id": "jambavan",
    "complexity": 3,
    "question": "ಜಾಂಬವಾನ್",
    "answer": "जाम्भवान",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Jāmbavān"
  },
  {
    "id": "vibhishana",
    "complexity": 3,
    "question": "ವಿಭೀಷಣ",
    "answer": "विभीषण",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Vibhīṣaṇa"
  },
  {
    "id": "parivar",
    "complexity": 3,
    "question": "ಪರಿವಾರ",
    "answer": "परिवार",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Parivār"
  },
  {
    "id": "sarak",
    "complexity": 3,
    "question": "ಸಡ಼ಕ",
    "answer": "सड़क",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Saṛak"
  },
  {
    "id": "bazar",
    "complexity": 3,
    "question": "ಬಾಜ಼ಾರ",
    "answer": "बाज़ार",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Bāzār"
  },
  {
    "id": "aspatal",
    "complexity": 3,
    "question": "ಅಸ್ಪತಾಲ",
    "answer": "अस्पताल",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Aspatāl"
  },
  {
    "id": "mandir",
    "complexity": 3,
    "question": "ಮಂದಿರ",
    "answer": "मंदिर",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Mandir"
  },
  {
    "id": "naukri",
    "complexity": 3,
    "question": "ನೌಕರೀ",
    "answer": "नौकरी",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Nauk­rī"
  },
  {
    "id": "samay",
    "complexity": 3,
    "question": "ಸಮಯ",
    "answer": "समय",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Samay"
  },
  {
    "id": "raat",
    "complexity": 3,
    "question": "ರಾತ",
    "answer": "रात",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Rāt"
  },
  {
    "id": "nariyal",
    "complexity": 3,
    "question": "ನಾರಿಯಲ",
    "answer": "नारियल",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Nāriyal"
  },
  {
    "id": "ananas",
    "complexity": 3,
    "question": "ಅನಾನಾಸ",
    "answer": "अनानास",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Anānās"
  },
  {
    "id": "angutha",
    "complexity": 3,
    "question": "ಅಂಗೂಠಾ",
    "answer": "अंगूठा",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Angūṭhā"
  },
  {
    "id": "mandodari",
    "complexity": 4,
    "question": "ಮಂದೋದರೀ",
    "answer": "मंदोदरी",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Mandodarī"
  },
  {
    "id": "meghanada",
    "complexity": 4,
    "question": "ಮೇಘನಾದ",
    "answer": "मेघनाद",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Meghanāda"
  },
  {
    "id": "indrajit",
    "complexity": 4,
    "question": "ಇಂದ್ರಜಿತ್",
    "answer": "इंद्रजित",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Indrajit"
  },
  {
    "id": "kumbhakarna",
    "complexity": 4,
    "question": "ಕುಂಭಕರ್ಣ",
    "answer": "कुंभकर्ण",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Kumbhakarṇa"
  },
  {
    "id": "shurpanakha",
    "complexity": 4,
    "question": "ಶೂರ್ಪಣಖಾ",
    "answer": "शूर्पणखा",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Śūrpaṇakhā"
  },
  {
    "id": "maricha",
    "complexity": 4,
    "question": "ಮಾರೀಚ",
    "answer": "मारिच",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Mārīca"
  },
  {
    "id": "tadaka",
    "complexity": 4,
    "question": "ತಾಡಕಾ",
    "answer": "ताड़का",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Tāḍakā"
  },
  {
    "id": "ahilya",
    "complexity": 4,
    "question": "ಅಹಿಲ್ಯಾ",
    "answer": "अहल्या",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Ahalyā"
  },
  {
    "id": "gautama",
    "complexity": 4,
    "question": "ಗೌತಮ",
    "answer": "गौतम",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Gautama"
  },
  {
    "id": "jatayu",
    "complexity": 4,
    "question": "ಜಟಾಯು",
    "answer": "जटायु",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Jaṭāyu"
  },
  {
    "id": "sampati",
    "complexity": 4,
    "question": "ಸಂಪಾತೀ",
    "answer": "संपाती",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Sampātī"
  },
  {
    "id": "shrutakirti",
    "complexity": 4,
    "question": "ಶ್ರುತಕೀರ್ತಿ",
    "answer": "श्रुतकीर्ति",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Shrutakirti"
  },
  {
    "id": "vashistha",
    "complexity": 4,
    "question": "ವಶಿಷ್ಠ",
    "answer": "वशिष्ठ",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Vashistha"
  },
  {
    "id": "trishira",
    "complexity": 4,
    "question": "ತ್ರಿಶಿರಾ",
    "answer": "त्रिशिरा",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Trishira"
  },
  {
    "id": "chamakdar",
    "complexity": 4,
    "question": "ಚಮಕದಾರ",
    "answer": "चमकदार",
    "notes": "Transliteration: Chamakdār"
  }
]